gpgway.com 2014-07-04

# GPG Privacy Statement

At Global Payroll Gateway, we recognize that privacy and security of personal financial information is a concern to our customers. We have taken the utmost care in establishing and implementing policies and procedures to protect this information. 

### Privacy Disclosure

This disclosure explains what information we collect about you, with whom we share it, and how you can direct us not to share certain information with certain parties. 

### Definitions

**We, our, and us:** means Global Payroll Gateway.

**You and your:** means customers using any services provided by Global Payroll Gateway.

**Nonpublic personal information:** means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. In this Statement document, we use the term “information” with respect to nonpublic personal information as defined by this section.

**Affiliate:** means a company which Global Payroll Gateway owns or controls, a company that owns or controls the Global Payroll Gateway, or a company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls Global Payroll Gateway.

**Opt out:** means to prevent certain sharing or use of information. We will explain how you can exercise this choice.

### Your Privacy is a Priority

We are committed to provide products, services, and offers of value to our customers. We may use information from our interactions with you and other customers, and from other parties, in providing services. Your privacy is considered in all aspects of our business. Our employees are informed of their responsibility to protect confidential customer information and are governed by a code of conduct that includes this confidentiality. Appropriate disciplinary policies are in place to help enforce employee privacy responsibilities. 

Security procedures and internal controls are also in place to protect our customers' privacy. We believe that the basis of each customer relationship is trust. Because you trust us with your personal information, we are committed to respect your privacy and safeguard that information. In order to preserve that trust, we pledge to protect your privacy by adhering to practices intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner. 

### Why we collect your information

Global Payroll Gateway receives and retains information about its customers through many sources. We limit the use and collection of this information to that which is necessary to maintain and administer financial services, provide excellent service, and offer new products and services that may be of benefit to our customers.

We gather information about you and your account so we can (a) deliver products and services to meet your needs, (b) know who you are and thereby prevent unauthorized access to your information, (c) design and improve the products we offer, (d) replace a lost card, PIN, or to provide some other form of assistance, and (e) comply with laws and regulations that govern us. 

### What information we collect

We may collect the following types of information about you:

Information we receive from you on applications or other forms

Information about your transactions with our affiliates or us

Information about your transactions with non-affiliated third parties

Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as verification of your identity and creditworthiness

We may also collect and disclose information about how users use our Web site, for example, by tracking unique views received by pages of the Web site or the domains from which users originate. This information is not personally identifiable. We may also use “cookies” to track returning users to our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the users’ PCs and use to identify the users should they visit the Web site again. Information collected may be associated with nonpublic personal information users provide us through our Web site.

### What information we disclose

We collect, use and share information about you so that we can provide the highest level of service to you for the services or products you use. We require companies to which we disclose non-public information about you to maintain its confidentiality.

We may share information we collect to our affiliates that offer financial services or additional products and services. In addition, we may disclose information we collect to companies, both affiliates and non-affiliates that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other companies with which we have joint marketing arrangements. We are also permitted under law to disclose non-public personal information about you to affiliates and "non-affiliated third parties" in certain circumstances. For example, we may disclose non-public personal information about you to companies that assist us in providing services to you.

In certain circumstances, in order to comply with government requirements or court orders, we are required to disclose information about you or your transactions. We will do this only when required by law, regulation or court order. We share only the information required.

Global Payroll Gateway is committed to fully complying with the laws and regulations, such as the Fair Credit Reporting Act and the Right to Financial Privacy Act, that have been established to protect the confidentiality of customer information. You are entitled to request credit reporting agencies to remove your name from lists supplied to us.

Global Payroll Gateway does exchange information about our customers with reputable information reporting agencies, in accordance with standard industry practice, to maximize the accuracy and security of such information and verify the existence and condition of customers' accounts. We do not share specific personal customer information with independent companies for any other purpose without the customer's consent, except when required by law, regulation, or court order, and to third party litigants when required by lawful judicial process or court order. 

### How to limit solicitations

From time to time, we or our affiliates or partners may call or write to tell you about products or services that we think may be of interest to you. You may tell us not to market products or services to you through telemarketing or direct mail marketing and not to provide your information to our affiliates or partners for marketing purposes by submitting a "no solicitation" request. You may, however, continue to receive promotional information in account related notices or other business purpose communications, including electronic announcements.

If you choose not to receive direct mail or telephone solicitations, please write to Customer Service at 18662 MacArthur Blvd., Suite 200, Irvine, CA 92612 and request that we do not solicit you through, or provide information about you to financial partners for telemarketing or direct mail marketing. 

### Protectiong your information on the Internet

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our privacy policy applies in its entirety to your Internet and PC transactions. 

### Privacy practices of third parties

Our website may feature links to third-party sites that offer goods, services, or information. We are not responsible for content or privacy policies or practices of any advertisers or linked sites of any third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policy before providing them with any personally identifiable information. Third party sites may collect and use information about you in a way that is different from this policy. 

### Confidentiality and Security

All Customer information is private and passed through a highly secured state-of-the-art SSL (Secured Socket Line). Our system is security focused that requires the leading 128-bit SSL certificates and Web sites solutions, Secure Site Services provide you with all of the authentication and encryption power.

We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to complete transactions or to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information such as encryption of account numbers and other sensitive data. 

### Close or Inactive Accounts

We will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice even after your account is closed or becomes inactive. 

### To change your election

If you would like to change a previous decision to limit direct marketing or sharing of nonpublic personal information please call us at the toll free phone number listed on our website or write us at the address listed above. 

### Additional Rights and Modifications

You may have other privacy protections under state laws, and we will comply with applicable state laws when we share information about you. We may amend this privacy notice at any time, and we will inform you of changes as required by law.
